<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of</string>
    <string name="tip_1_title">Write Readable Code</string>
    <string name="tip_1_info">Employ meaningful variable and function names, maintain consistent formatting, and utilize comments to clarify intricate logic.</string>
    <string name="tip_2_title">Utilize Version Control</string>
    <string name="tip_2_info">Make use of a version control system like Git to track code changes and facilitate collaboration with others.</string>
    <string name="tip_3_info">Before delving into coding, ensure a comprehensive understanding of the problem at hand. Break it down into smaller components if necessary.</string>
    <string name="tip_4_info">Outline the steps or algorithms you will employ to solve the problem before writing the actual code. Pseudocode aids in organizing your thought process.</string>
    <string name="tip_5_info">Avoid code duplication by utilizing functions, classes, and reusable components to encapsulate common functionality.</string>
    <string name="tip_6_info">Create automated tests to verify code correctness and catch bugs during development</string>
    <string name="tip_7_info">When encountering errors, provide clear and descriptive error messages to facilitate effective debugging.</string>
    <string name="tip_8_info">Utilize tools such as debuggers, logging, and print statements to identify and rectify code issues.</string>
    <string name="tip_9_info">Take advantage of existing libraries and frameworks to avoid reinventing the wheel and expedite development.</string>
    <string name="tip_10_info">Invest time in understanding the documentation of the programming language, libraries, and tools you are utilizing.</string>
    <string name="tip_11_info">Prioritize writing clean and maintainable code. Only optimize for performance when necessary and based on profiling data.</string>
    <string name="tip_12_info">Familiarize yourself with keyboard shortcuts specific to your development environment, significantly enhancing productivity.</string>
    <string name="tip_13_info">When committing changes to version control, furnish concise and clear messages documenting the purpose of the modifications.</string>
    <string name="tip_14_info">Regularly update the dependencies in your project to benefit from bug fixes, security patches, and new features.</string>
    <string name="tip_15_info">Seek feedback from peers through code reviews to learn from others, enhance code quality, and identify potential issues.</string>
    <string name="tip_16_info">Follow established coding conventions for your chosen programming language, promoting consistency and readability.</string>
    <string name="tip_17_info">Utilize automated tools that enforce coding standards, identify common errors, and ensure consistent code formatting.</string>
    <string name="tip_18_info">Stack traces offer valuable insights into the location of errors, aiding in the identification of root causes.</string>
    <string name="tip_19_info">Partition your code into modular components with clearly defined responsibilities, communicating through well-defined interfaces.</string>
    <string name="tip_20_info">Avoid intertwining data and logic. Instead, organize code and data into appropriate structures such as classes, modules, or databases to enhance maintainability and clarity.</string>
    <string name="tip_21_info">Familiarize yourself with common data structures and algorithms to make informed decisions when designing your code.</string>
    <string name="tip_22_info">Choose the most efficient data structure that suits your needs, considering factors such as performance and memory usage.</string>
    <string name="tip_23_info">Take into account all possible scenarios and ensure your code gracefully handles edge cases and input validation.</string>
    <string name="tip_24_info">Utilize profiling tools to identify performance bottlenecks and optimize the most time-consuming parts of your code.</string>
    <string name="tip_25_info">Cache expensive or frequently accessed data to minimize unnecessary computations and enhance overall performance.</string>
    <string name="tip_26_info">Parameterize your code by using variables or configuration files instead of hardcoding values. This promotes flexibility and maintainability.</string>
    <string name="tip_27_info">Programming is a dynamic field that constantly evolves. Stay up to date with new technologies, programming languages, and best practices.</string>
    <string name="tip_28_info">When faced with a large problem, break it down into smaller, manageable tasks. Solve each task individually and integrate them later.</string>
    <string name="tip_29_info">Effective use of documentation provides valuable insights into the proper utilization of libraries, frameworks, and programming tools.</string>
    <string name="tip_30_info">Establish a well-structured folder hierarchy, employ meaningful file names, and document your code to facilitate navigation and understanding.</string>
    <string name="tip_3_title">Grasp the Problem</string>
    <string name="tip_4_title">Plan and Use Pseudocode</string>
    <string name="tip_5_title">Embrace the DRY Principle (Don’t Repeat Yourself)</string>
    <string name="tip_6_title">Test Early and Frequently</string>
    <string name="tip_7_title">Employ Meaningful Error Messages</string>
    <string name="tip_8_title">Utilize Debugging Techniques</string>
    <string name="tip_9_title">Leverage Libraries and Frameworks</string>
    <string name="tip_10_title">Thoroughly Read the Documentation</string>
    <string name="tip_11_title">Avoid Premature Optimization</string>
    <string name="tip_12_title">Master Keyboard Shortcuts</string>
    <string name="tip_13_title">Provide Descriptive Commit Messages</string>
    <string name="tip_14_title">Keep Dependencies Up to Date</string>
    <string name="tip_15_title">Embrace Code Reviews</string>
    <string name="tip_16_title">Adhere to Coding Conventions</string>
    <string name="tip_17_title">Employ Linting and Formatting Tools</string>
    <string name="tip_18_title">Master Reading Stack Traces</string>
    <string name="tip_19_title">Practice Modular Design</string>
    <string name="tip_20_title">Separate Code and Data</string>
    <string name="tip_21_title">Understand Data Structures and Algorithms</string>
    <string name="tip_22_title">Optimize Data Structures</string>
    <string name="tip_23_title">Handle Edge Cases</string>
    <string name="tip_24_title">Profile Your Code</string>
    <string name="tip_25_title">Implement Caching and Memoization</string>
    <string name="tip_26_title">Avoid Hardcoding Values</string>
    <string name="tip_27_title">Stay Curious and Keep Learning</string>
    <string name="tip_28_title">Break Down Complex Tasks</string>
    <string name="tip_29_title">Master the Art of Reading and Understanding Documentation</string>
    <string name="tip_30_title">Maintain an Organized Codebase</string>

</resources>